{
    "subject": "resource/Stan_Rosenberg",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/description",
    "object": "American politician",
    "human_readable": "The description of Stan Rosenberg is American politician.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8383816480636597,
            "question": "What is the role of a politician like Stan Rosenberg in American society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5822007656097412,
            "question": "What are some current political issues that Stan Rosenberg might be involved with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5813122391700745,
            "question": "What is Stan Rosenberg's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295203924179077,
            "question": "What political party does Stan Rosenberg likely belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5146646499633789,
            "question": "What are some challenges that politicians like Stan Rosenberg face?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4290640950202942,
            "question": "How can citizens engage with and influence the work of politicians like Stan Rosenberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42584291100502014,
            "question": "Where is Stan Rosenberg from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2940780222415924,
            "question": "Can you name any notable achievements of Stan Rosenberg?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2806374430656433,
            "question": "Are there any organizations or groups that Stan Rosenberg works with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23444680869579315,
            "question": "How does Stan Rosenberg's work impact the lives of ordinary citizens?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The description of Stan Rosenberg is American politician.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1458_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any organizations or groups that Stan Rosenberg works with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1458_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name any notable achievements of Stan Rosenberg?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1458_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Stan Rosenberg from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1458_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1458_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents describe Stan Rosenberg as a Massachusetts state legislator and Senate President, making him an American politician. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. According to the documents, Stan Rosenberg served as a state Senator and President Pro Tem of the Massachusetts Senate, which suggests that he is indeed an American politician."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide substantial information about Stan Rosenberg, including his career as a Massachusetts state legislator and his role as the Senate president. This supports the description of him as an American politician."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}